Bill Pelke Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Publications, 1974-2003, Undated; nam_apap205-2; 1.15 cubic feet
  - " A Layperson's Guide for Communication with People in Prison " - by Mark D. Fronckiewicz, 1993; nam_apap205-2_53 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - " Leaven of Forgiveness " by Mary Sue Penn, 1997; nam_apap205-2_54 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - " Life and Liberty " by Vasu Murti, Undated; nam_apap205-2_55 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Los Angeles Reader, September 29, 1995; nam_apap205-2_56 (Oversize 7, Folder 4)
  - Loyola University Chicago Law Journal, 1996; nam_apap205-2_57 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Mandala, 2000; nam_apap205-2_58 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - The Messenger, 1995; nam_apap205-2_59 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - National Catholic Reader, March 31, 1989; nam_apap205-2_60 (Oversize 7, Folder 5)
  - Ne Deja Vu Pas- A Collection of Poetr y - by Trovatore Poetaster, 1991; nam_apap205-2_61 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - " The New Creature in Christ " - Bilble Study Series by Mark D. Fronkiewicz and William J. Kitchens, Undated; nam_apap205-2_62 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - New York, 1988; nam_apap205-2_63 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - " New Yorkers want an Alternative to the Death Penalty ", by William J. Bowers and Margaret Vandiver, 1991; nam_apap205-2_64 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Newsweek, 1990; nam_apap205-2_65 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Northeastern University Press - New Books, 1995; nam_apap205-2_66 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Notre Dame Magazine, 1997; nam_apap205-2_67 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - OGGI, 1988; nam_apap205-2_68 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - " The O. J. Simpson Case and Capital Punishment " - Howard Law Journal, 1995; nam_apap205-2_69 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - The Only Voice, June, 1993; nam_apap205-2_70 (Oversize 7, Folder 6)
  - The Orlando Sentinel, April 19, 1998; nam_apap205-2_71 (Oversize 7, Folder 7)
  - The Other Side, 1993; nam_apap205-2_72 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - The Other Side, 1994; nam_apap205-2_73 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - The Other Side, 1994; nam_apap205-2_74 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - The Other Side, 1994; nam_apap205-2_75 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - The Other Side's - Faces of Faith, 1990; nam_apap205-2_76 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer, October 4, 1987; nam_apap205-2_77 (Oversize 7, Folder 8)
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer, September 18, 1994; nam_apap205-2_78 (Oversize 7, Folder 9)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1995; nam_apap205-2_79 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1995; nam_apap205-2_80 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1995; nam_apap205-2_81 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - The Philadelphia Trumpet, 1999; nam_apap205-2_82 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - " The Possible Pain Experienced During Execution by Different Methods ", 1993; nam_apap205-2_83 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - " Promoting Mutual Forgiveness within the Fractured Relationship " by Everett L. Worthington, Jr., 1990; nam_apap205-2_84 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - " Question of Violation of Human Rights and Fundamental Freedoms " - Commission on Human Rights, 1998; nam_apap205-2_85 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - " Refocusing the Death Penalty Discussion in America " - American Bar Association, 1998; nam_apap205-2_86 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - " Security the Soul on the Death Penalty ", 1998; nam_apap205-2_87 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - SPIN, November, 1991; nam_apap205-2_88 (Oversize 7, Folder 10)
  - The Story the time Couldn't tell - Church of Scientology, 1991; nam_apap205-2_89 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Ten Basic Responsibilities of Nonprofit Boards by Richard T. Ingram, 1996; nam_apap205-2_90 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Thomas M. Cooley Law Review - Death Penalty Symposium, 1996; nam_apap205-2_91 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Time, 1992; nam_apap205-2_92 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - We, On Death Row, 2000; nam_apap205-2_93 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - The White House Report to students, ca.1985; nam_apap205-2_94 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Whole Life Times, April, 1995; nam_apap205-2_95 (Oversize 7, Folder 11)
  - " Yeah, Clementine ", by H.L. " Willie " Otey, 1991; nam_apap205-2_96 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- MVFR/Journey of Hope, 1990-2005, Undated; nam_apap205-3; 3.26 cubic feet
  This series contains supplemental material to the Murder Victims Families For Reconciliation Records collected by Bill Pelke during his tenure as a board member of that organization. Included in this series are administrative records, correspondence, promotional materials, documents relating to Bill Pelkes time as editor of MVFRs newsletter The Voice including drafts and layouts, and folders relating to the Journey of Hope events from 1993-1999 assembled by Bill Pelke.
  - Correspondence, 1991; 1993-1994; 1998; Undated; nam_apap205-3_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Journey of Hope, 1993; nam_apap205-3_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Journey of Hope, 1994; nam_apap205-3_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Journey of Hope, 1995; nam_apap205-3_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Journey of Hope, 1997; nam_apap205-3_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Journey of Hope, 1998; nam_apap205-3_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Journey of Hope, 1998; nam_apap205-3_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Journey of Hope, 1999; nam_apap205-3_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Journey of Hope, Undated; nam_apap205-3_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Journey of Hope - Articles of Incorporation, 1998; nam_apap205-3_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 1993; nam_apap205-3_11 (Oversize 3, Item 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 1995; nam_apap205-3_12 (Oversize 3, Item 3)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 1998; nam_apap205-3_13 (Oversize 2, Item 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2000; nam_apap205-3_14 (Oversize 2, Item 4)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2001; nam_apap205-3_15 (Oversize 1, Item 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2001; nam_apap205-3_16 (Oversize 1, Item 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2003; nam_apap205-3_17 (Oversize 1, Item 3)
  - Journey of Hope - Black T-shirt, 2005; nam_apap205-3_18 (Oversize 1, Item 4)
  - Journey of Hope - Bumper Sticker, Undated; nam_apap205-3_19 (Oversize 5, Item 14)
  - Journey of Hope - Business Card, Undated; nam_apap205-3_20 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Journey of Hope - Button, 1993; nam_apap205-3_21 (Oversize 5, Item 7)
  - Journey of Hope - Button, 1994; nam_apap205-3_22 (Oversize 5, Item 8)
  - Journey of Hope - Button, 1998; nam_apap205-3_23 (Oversize 5, Item 9)
  - Journey of Hope - California Journey Account, 1996; nam_apap205-3_24 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Journey of Hope - Conference Call, May 23, 1995; nam_apap205-3_25 (Oversize 9, Cassette 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Final Night Video (part 1), October 16, 1996; nam_apap205-3_26 (Oversize 9, Vhs 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Final Night Video (part 2), October 16, 1996; nam_apap205-3_27 (Oversize 9, Vhs 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Georgia Packet, 1994; nam_apap205-3_28 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Journey of Hope - Georgia Packet, 1994; nam_apap205-3_29 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Journey of Hope - Gray T-shirt, 1996; nam_apap205-3_30 (Oversize 2, Item 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Members, 1993; nam_apap205-3_31 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Journey of Hope - Notes, 1995; nam_apap205-3_32 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Journey of Hope - Organizing Handbook, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-3_33 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Journey of Hope - Organizing Handbook, Undated; nam_apap205-3_34 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Journey of Hope - Poster, 1993; nam_apap205-3_35 (Flat-file 5)
  - Journey of Hope - Press Packet, 2003; nam_apap205-3_36 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Journey of Hope - Promotional Material, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-3_37 (Oversize 7, Folder 1)
  - Journey of Hope - White T-shirt, 1994; nam_apap205-3_38 (Oversize 3, Item 2)
  - Journey of Hope - White T-shirt, 1995; nam_apap205-3_39 (Oversize 3, Item 4)
  - Journey of Hope - White T-shirt, 1999; nam_apap205-3_40 (Oversize 2, Item 3)
  - MVFR - ACLU Letter to Congress, 1994; nam_apap205-3_41 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - MVFR - Business Card Holder, Undated; nam_apap205-3_42 (Oversize 5, Item 5)
  - MVFR - Business Cards, Undated; nam_apap205-3_43 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - MVFR - Board, 1990; nam_apap205-3_44 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - MVFR - Board, 1993; nam_apap205-3_45 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - MVFR - Board, 1994; nam_apap205-3_46 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - MVFR - Board, 1995; nam_apap205-3_47 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - MVFR - Board, 1996; nam_apap205-3_48 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - MVFR - Board, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-3_49 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - MVFR - Board, Undated; nam_apap205-3_50 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - MVFR - By- Laws, Undated; nam_apap205-3_51 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - MVFR - Constitutional Amendment, 1996; nam_apap205-3_52 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - MVFR - Dead Man Walking Concert, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-3_53 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - MVFR - Directors Report, 1996; nam_apap205-3_54 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - MVRF - Drafts, 1992-1993; 1995; Undated; nam_apap205-3_55 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - MVRF - Drafts, 1992-1994; 1996; Undated; nam_apap205-3_56 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - MVRF - Finances, 1992; nam_apap205-3_57 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - MVRF - Finances, 1993; nam_apap205-3_58 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - MVFR - Finances, 1994; nam_apap205-3_59 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - MVFR - Finances, 1995; nam_apap205-3_60 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - MVFR - Finances, 1998; nam_apap205-3_61 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - MVFR - Internships, 1993; nam_apap205-3_62 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - MVFR - Mailing Lists, Undated; nam_apap205-3_63 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - MVFR - Members List, Undated; nam_apap205-3_64 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - MVFR - Membership Committee, Undated; nam_apap205-3_65 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - MVFR - Mission Statement, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-3_66 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - MVFR - " Not in Our Name ", 1998-1999; nam_apap205-3_67 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - MVFR - Pelke Notes, Undated; nam_apap205-3_68 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - MVFR - Petition Form - Blank, Undated; nam_apap205-3_69 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - MVFR - Press Conference, 1994; nam_apap205-3_70 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - MVFR - Promotional Material, 1993; Undated; nam_apap205-3_71 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - MVFR - Restorative Justice Proposal, Undated; nam_apap205-3_72 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1992; nam_apap205-3_73 (Oversize 7, Folder 2)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1994; nam_apap205-3_74 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1995; nam_apap205-3_75 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - MVFR- The Voice, 1997; nam_apap205-3_76 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - MVFR - The Voice Draft, 1992; nam_apap205-3_77 (Oversize 7, Folder 3)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated; nam_apap205-3_78 (Oversize 5, Item 1)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated; nam_apap205-3_79 (Oversize 5, Item 2)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated; nam_apap205-3_80 (Oversize 5, Item 3)
  - MVFR - Wooden Ornament, Undated; nam_apap205-3_81 (Oversize 5, Item 4)
- Amnesty International, 1988-2000, Undated; nam_apap205-4; 3.75 cubic feet
  This series documents Bill Pelkes involvement in Amnesty International. Included in this sub-series are Amnesty International and Amnesty International USA (AIUSA) documents related to Bill Pelkes role as Indianas State Death Penalty Abolition Coordinator, newsletters, annual conference documents, annual reports, correspondence, flyers, pamphlets, and other outreach materials collected by Bill Pelke.
  - The ABC's of Abolition, Undated; nam_apap205-4_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abolition Network News, 1999; nam_apap205-4_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Action Alert, 1992; nam_apap205-4_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Action Alert on Federal Death Penalty, Undated; nam_apap205-4_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Activator, 1991; nam_apap205-4_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Activator, 1992; nam_apap205-4_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Activator, 1993; nam_apap205-4_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Activator, 1994; nam_apap205-4_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Activator, 1995; nam_apap205-4_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Activator, 1996; nam_apap205-4_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Activity and Campaign Calendar for 1995-1996, nam_apap205-4_11 (Oversize 8, Folder 1)
  - Amnesty Action, 1989; 1992-1994; nam_apap205-4_12 (Oversize 8, Folder 2)
  - Amnesty Action Bulletin Board, Undated; nam_apap205-4_13 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Amnesty Break, 1996; nam_apap205-4_14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AIMLL: Amnesty International Membersz for Lesbian and Gay Concerns, 1993; nam_apap205-4_15 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Amnesty International Policy Forum, 1992-1993; nam_apap205-4_16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Amnesty Now, 1997-2000; nam_apap205-4_17 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Analysis of 1994 Local Group Activity, 1995; nam_apap205-4_18 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Action File Report, 1993-1995; nam_apap205-4_19 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Conference, Undated; nam_apap205-4_20 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1988; nam_apap205-4_21 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1991; nam_apap205-4_22 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1992; nam_apap205-4_23 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1993; nam_apap205-4_24 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1994; nam_apap205-4_25 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1995; nam_apap205-4_26 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1996; nam_apap205-4_27 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1997; nam_apap205-4_28 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1998; nam_apap205-4_29 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Annual General Meeting, 1999; nam_apap205-4_30 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Annual General Meeting, 2000; nam_apap205-4_31 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Annual Local Group Report, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-4_32 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, 1995; nam_apap205-4_33 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Annual Report, 1996; nam_apap205-4_34 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, 1997; nam_apap205-4_35 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 1998; nam_apap205-4_36 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Appeals Cases, 1994; nam_apap205-4_37 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Background Information World Conference on Human Rights, 1993; nam_apap205-4_38 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Balkans Region, Undated; nam_apap205-4_39 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors, 1995-1996; nam_apap205-4_40 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Brochures, 1991-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-4_41 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Budget and Bookkeeping Guidelines, ca.1994; nam_apap205-4_42 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Budget and Bookkeeping Guidelines, 1995; nam_apap205-4_43 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Budget and Bookkeeping Guidelines, 1996; nam_apap205-4_44 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bylaws, 1992; nam_apap205-4_45 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Calendar, 1995-2000; nam_apap205-4_46 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Calendar of Human Rights Events in Los Angeles, 1992; nam_apap205-4_47 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Campaigns Against the Execution of Junvenile Offenders, 1992; nam_apap205-4_48 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - The Case of Mumia Abu - Jamal, 1995; nam_apap205-4_49 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Casework Manual, 1995; nam_apap205-4_50 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Challenge to Leadership, 1993; nam_apap205-4_51 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - China MFN Crisis Response, 1994; nam_apap205-4_52 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Complaint Procedures Questionnaire, 1994; nam_apap205-4_53 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Conditions for Death Row Prisoners in the H - Unit Oklahoma State Penitentiary, 1994; nam_apap205-4_54 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1988; nam_apap205-4_55 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, 1989; nam_apap205-4_56 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1991; nam_apap205-4_57 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1992; nam_apap205-4_58 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, 1993; nam_apap205-4_59 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, 1994; nam_apap205-4_60 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, 1995; nam_apap205-4_61 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, 1996; nam_apap205-4_62 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence, 1997; nam_apap205-4_63 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, 1998; nam_apap205-4_64 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence, Undated; nam_apap205-4_65 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Death Penalty Abolition Institute, 1995; nam_apap205-4_66 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Death Penalty Abolitionists' Questionnaire from hell, Undated; nam_apap205-4_67 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Death Penalty Actions, 1992-1993; nam_apap205-4_68 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Death Penalty Advisory Committee, 1995; nam_apap205-4_69 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Death Penalty Director Research, 1994; nam_apap205-4_70 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Death Penalty Education and Action Packet, ca.1995; nam_apap205-4_71 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - The Death Penalty in Texas, 1998; nam_apap205-4_72 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Death Penalty Institute, 1997; nam_apap205-4_73 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - " Death Penalty is a Symbol not a Solution ", Undated; nam_apap205-4_74 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1991; nam_apap205-4_75 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1992; nam_apap205-4_76 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1993; nam_apap205-4_77 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1994; nam_apap205-4_78 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Death Penalty Mailing, 1995; nam_apap205-4_79 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-4_80 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-4_81 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-4_82 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AI USA - Death Penalty Newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-4_83 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Death Penalty Objectives, Midwest Region, 1995-1996; nam_apap205-4_84 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Death Penalty Worldwide, 1997; nam_apap205-4_85 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Developments on the Death Penalty During 1994, 1995; nam_apap205-4_86 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Draft of Long Range Plan, ca.1995; nam_apap205-4_87 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Election, 1992-1995; nam_apap205-4_88 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Events Schedule, 1992-1993; nam_apap205-4_89 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - " Execute Justice Not People ", Undated; nam_apap205-4_90 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Feedback Form, Undated; nam_apap205-4_91 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Finance Guidelines, 1994; nam_apap205-4_92 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Finance Guidelines, 1995; nam_apap205-4_93 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Financal Guidelines, 1996; nam_apap205-4_94 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Flyers, 1991-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-4_95 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Focus, 1991; 1994; nam_apap205-4_96 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Follow Up to Open Letter to President on the Death Penalty, 1995; nam_apap205-4_97 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Form, letters, and petitions, 1991; 1993; 1995; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-4_98 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Freedom in the Balance, 1995; nam_apap205-4_99 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - French Group 186 - Against the Death Penalty Banner, Undated; nam_apap205-4_100 (Roll 1, Item 1)
  - Funding Amnesty's Human Rights work, 1992; nam_apap205-4_101 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fundraising for Human Rights, 1992; nam_apap205-4_102 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Funds for Freedom, Undated; nam_apap205-4_103 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - General, 1990-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-4_104 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - General, 1990-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-4_105 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Ginetta Sagan Fund, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-4_106 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Group 22 Newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-4_107 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Haiti, 1994; nam_apap205-4_108 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Help with Journey, Undated; nam_apap205-4_109 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Holiday Card Action, 1993-1995; 1998; nam_apap205-4_110 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Human Rights and American Indians, 1992; nam_apap205-4_111 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Human Rights and the Presidential Elections, 1996; nam_apap205-4_112 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Human Rights and U.S. Security Assistance, 1993; nam_apap205-4_113 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Human Rights Educators Network, 1997; nam_apap205-4_114 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - " Human Rights for Children ", Undated; nam_apap205-4_115 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Human Rights Have No Borders - Hat, Undated; nam_apap205-4_116 (Oversize 4, Item 2)
  - Human Rights Library, 1991; nam_apap205-4_117 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Imminent Execution of Juvenile Offender (Update), 1993; nam_apap205-4_118 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - In Grant Placements, 1993; nam_apap205-4_119 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Inside the Mandate, 1995; 1998; nam_apap205-4_120 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Interact, 1997; nam_apap205-4_121 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - International Council Meeting, 1997; nam_apap205-4_122 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - International Week of Student Action, 1998; nam_apap205-4_123 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Ivan Morris Fund, Undated; nam_apap205-4_124 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Job Announcements, 1992-1995; 1997; Undated; nam_apap205-4_125 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Leadership List, 1995; nam_apap205-4_126 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Leadership Survey, Undated; nam_apap205-4_127 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Legislative Update, 1994-1995; nam_apap205-4_128 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Lillehaug Project, 1993; nam_apap205-4_129 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - The Lives Behind the Lies: The Campaign Against " Disappearances " and Political Killings, 1993; nam_apap205-4_130 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Local Group Charter, Undated; nam_apap205-4_131 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Local Group Resources, 1995; nam_apap205-4_132 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Lobbying for Abolition Guide, Undated; nam_apap205-4_133 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Medical Death Penalty Newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-4_134 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Meeting in Houston, ca.1994; nam_apap205-4_135 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Member Questionnaire on Improving, nam_apap205-4_136 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Members List, 1992-1994; nam_apap205-4_137 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Memorandum, 1990; 1992-1996; nam_apap205-4_138 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Merchandise Order Form, ca.1992; 1993-1994; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-4_139 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Midwest Regional Conference, 1994-1995; nam_apap205-4_140 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Midwest Regional Leadership Meeting, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-4_141 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Midwest Regional News, 1997; nam_apap205-4_142 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Midwest Regional News, 1998; nam_apap205-4_143 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Midwest Region Death Penalty Update, 1995; nam_apap205-4_144 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Midwest Region Newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-4_145 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Midwest Region Newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-4_146 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Midwest Region SDPAC, 1992-1993; nam_apap205-4_147 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Military, Security, Police Working Group, 1996; nam_apap205-4_148 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Missouri Action Request, 1993; nam_apap205-4_149 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-4_150 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1994-1995; nam_apap205-4_151 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1995; nam_apap205-4_152 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1995-1996; nam_apap205-4_153 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1996; nam_apap205-4_154 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1996; nam_apap205-4_155 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-4_156 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-4_157 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1998; nam_apap205-4_158 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1998; nam_apap205-4_159 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1998-1999; nam_apap205-4_160 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Monthly Mailing, 1999; nam_apap205-4_161 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Monthly Mailing, 2000; nam_apap205-4_162 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Multi - Cultural Human Rights Symposium, 1994; nam_apap205-4_163 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - National Casework Program, 1996; nam_apap205-4_164 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - National Recruitment Drive, 1997; nam_apap205-4_165 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - National Weak of Student Action, 2000; nam_apap205-4_166 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-4_167 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-4_168 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-4_169 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-4_170 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-4_171 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-4_172 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Newsletter, 2000; nam_apap205-4_173 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - News Release, 1994-1996; 1998; nam_apap205-4_174 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Ohio/ Indiana Area Meeting Schedule, Undated; nam_apap205-4_175 (Box 2, Folder 94)